[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0330_0101_d_00_container_asgoodasmyword",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0330_Ranger01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_16",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_objective_title",
  "Description": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0330_0101_asgoodasmyword_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0330_0102_d_00_container_mappingtheedgeofdespair",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0330_Ranger01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_17",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_16 && (99D_MSQ_07 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_objective_title",
  "Description": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0330_0102_mappingtheedgeofdespair_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0330_0103_d_00_container_pickingupthepieces",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0330_Ranger01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_18",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_17",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_objective_title",
  "Description": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0330_0103_pickingupthepieces_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0331_0101_d_00_container_thebalemawbeast",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0331_Tracker",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_20",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_objective_title",
  "Description": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0331_0101_thebalemawbeast_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0331_0102_d_00_container_wolvesofwinter",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0331_Tracker",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_21",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_20",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_objective_title",
  "Description": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0331_0102_wolvesofwinter_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0331_0103_d_00_container_thebeastreturns",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0331_Tracker",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_22",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_21 && (99D_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_objective_title",
  "Description": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0331_0103_thebeastreturns_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0332_0101_d_00_container_aspotofluxury",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0332_Furrier00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_23",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_objective_title",
  "Description": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0332_0101_aspotofluxury_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0332_0102_d_00_container_fabulousfurs",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0332_Furrier02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_24",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_23 && (99D_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_objective_title",
  "Description": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0332_0102_fabulousfurs_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0332_0103_puredelight",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0332_0103_d_00_container_puredelight",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0332_Furrier02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_25",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_24",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0332_0103_puredelight_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0332_0103_puredelight_objective_title",
  "Description": "0332_0103_puredelight_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0332_0103_puredelight_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0332_0103_puredelight_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0332_0103_puredelight_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0332_0103_puredelight_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0333_0101_whiteasbone",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0333_0101_d_00_container_whiteasbone",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0333_Arcanist",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_26",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_objective_title",
  "Description": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0333_0101_whiteasbone_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0333_0102_redasblood",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0333_0102_d_00_container_redasblood",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0333_Arcanist01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_27",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_26 && (99D_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0333_0102_redasblood_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0333_0102_redasblood_objective_title",
  "Description": "0333_0102_redasblood_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0333_0102_redasblood_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0333_0102_redasblood_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0333_0102_redasblood_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0333_0102_redasblood_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0333_0103_blackasebony",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0333_0103_d_00_container_blackasebony",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0333_Arcanist01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_28",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_27 && (99D_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0333_0103_blackasebony_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0333_0103_blackasebony_objective_title",
  "Description": "0333_0103_blackasebony_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0333_0103_blackasebony_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0333_0103_blackasebony_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0333_0103_blackasebony_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0333_0103_blackasebony_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0333_0104_d_00_container_anofferingforoffspring",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0333_Arcanist01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_29",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_28",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_objective_title",
  "Description": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0333_0104_anofferingforoffspring_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0334_0101_d_00_container_perfectpiroshkis",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0334_Baker01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_30",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_objective_title",
  "Description": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0334_0101_perfectpiroshkis_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0334_0102_d_00_container_towarmthesoulwardens",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99D_PedroCarrillo_B",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_Quest_31",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_30 && (99D_MSQ_08 || 99_MSQ_56)",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_objective_title",
  "Description": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0334_0102_towarmthesoulwardens_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0501_PrimeResolve",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_00_Containter_weaponwrapperquest",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_00",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0501_PrimeResolve_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0501_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0501_b_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0319_0501_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0319_0501_c_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0319_0501_e_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0319_0501_f_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0502_PROne",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0502_PROneSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0502_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0502_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0503_PRTwo",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0503_PRTwoSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0503_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0503_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0504_PRThree",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0504_PRThreeSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0504_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0504_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0505_PRFour",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0505_PRFourSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0505_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0505_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0506_PRFive",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0506_PRFiveSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0506_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0506_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0507_PRSix",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0507_PRSixSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0507_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0507_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0508_PRSeven",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0508_PRSevenSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0508_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0508_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0319_0509_PREight",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0509_PREightSuccess",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0319_0509_a_Title",
  "Description": "0319_0509_b_Description"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0101_d_00_container_GlimmeringMercy",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_00",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0102_Prelude",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0102_d_00_container_Prelude",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0102_Prelude_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0102_Prelude_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0102_Prelude_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0102_Prelude_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0102_Prelude_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0102_Prelude_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0103_Adagio",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0103_d_00_container_Adagio",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0103_Adagio_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0103_Adagio_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0103_Adagio_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0103_Adagio_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0103_Adagio_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0103_Adagio_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0104_Scherzo",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0104_d_00_container_Scherzo",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0104_Scherzo_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0104_Scherzo_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0104_Scherzo_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0104_Scherzo_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0104_Scherzo_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0104_Scherzo_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0105_Shanty",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0105_d_00_container_Shanty",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0105_Shanty_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0105_Shanty_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0105_Shanty_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0105_Shanty_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0105_Shanty_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0105_Shanty_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0106_Zarabanda",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0106_d_00_container_Zarabanda",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0107_Requiem",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0107_d_00_container_Requiem",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0107_Requiem_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0107_Requiem_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0107_Requiem_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0107_Requiem_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0107_Requiem_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0107_Requiem_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0108_Passepied",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0108_d_00_container_Passepied",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0108_Passepied_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0108_Passepied_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0108_Passepied_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0108_Passepied_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0108_Passepied_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0108_Passepied_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0320_0109_Sonata",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0320_0109_d_00_container_Sonata",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0109_Sonata_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0320_0109_Sonata_objective_title",
  "Description": "0320_0109_Sonata_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0320_0109_Sonata_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0320_0109_Sonata_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0320_0109_Sonata_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0101_AzureRavager",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0101_d_00_container_AzureRavager",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_00",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0102_d_00_container_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0103_d_00_container_AzureRavager_byrootandbough",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0104_d_00_container_AzureRavager_sampleofevil",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0105_d_00_container_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0106_d_00_container_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0107_d_00_container_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0108_d_00_container_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0321_0109_d_00_container_AzureRavager_gleamingedge",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0321_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_objective_title",
  "Description": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0201_RampantConviction",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0201_d_00_container_RampantConviction",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_00",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0202_d_00_container_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0203_d_00_container_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0204_d_00_container_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0205_d_00_container_RampantConviction_forestsheart",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0206_d_00_container_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0207_d_00_container_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0208_d_00_container_RampantConviction_avileharvest",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0318_0209_d_00_container_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0318_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_objective_title",
  "Description": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0101_RL_00",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0101_RL_00_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_00",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0101_RL_00_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_00_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_00_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0325_0101_RL_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0325_0101_RL_00_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0325_0101_RL_00_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0325_0101_RL_00_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0102_RL_01",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0102_RL_01_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0102_RL_01_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_01_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_01_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0103_RL_02",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0103_RL_02_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0103_RL_02_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_02_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_02_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0104_RL_03",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0104_RL_03_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0104_RL_03_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_03_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_03_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0105_RL_04",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0105_RL_04_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0105_RL_04_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_04_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_04_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0106_RL_05",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0106_RL_05_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0106_RL_05_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_05_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_05_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0107_RL_06",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0107_RL_06_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0107_RL_06_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_06_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_06_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0108_RL_07",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0108_RL_07_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0108_RL_07_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_07_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_07_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0325_0109_RL_08",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0325_0109_RL_08_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0109_RL_08_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0325_0101_RL_08_objective_title",
  "Description": "0325_0101_RL_08_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0301_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0301_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0302_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0302_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0303_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0303_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0304_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0304_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0305_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0305_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0306_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0306_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0307_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0307_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0308_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0308_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0309_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0309_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0310_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0310_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0301_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0301_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0302_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0302_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0303_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0303_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0304_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0304_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0305_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0305_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0306_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0306_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0307_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0307_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0308_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0308_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0309_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0309_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0310_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0310_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0301_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0301_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0302_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0302_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0303_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0303_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0304_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0304_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0305_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0305_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0306_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0306_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0307_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0307_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0308_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0308_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0309_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0309_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0310_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0310_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0361_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0361_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0362_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0362_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0363_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0363_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0364_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0364_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0365_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0365_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0366_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0366_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0367_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0367_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0368_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0368_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0369_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0369_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0370_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0370_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0361_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0361_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0362_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0362_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0363_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0363_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0364_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0364_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0365_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0365_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0366_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0366_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0367_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0367_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0368_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0368_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0369_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0369_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0370_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0370_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0361_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0361_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0362_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0362_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0363_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0363_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0364_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0364_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0365_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0365_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0366_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0366_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0367_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0367_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0368_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0368_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0369_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0369_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0370_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0370_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_01_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_03_H_01_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_02_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_03_H_02_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_03_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_03_H_03_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "03_Kazu",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_objective_title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_04_WulfstanGlyphs_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "03_Kazu_1",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_SQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_objective_title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_05_MokoshGlyphs_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "03_Simone",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_objective_title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_06_AscensionCurse_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 42,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "03_Hotspur_B",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_01_PassingGood_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 42,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "03_Hotspur_C",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "03_SQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_02_ArmedPoints_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 46,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99D_ChangZhen_A",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "03_SQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_05&&03_SQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Title",
  "Description": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "03_SQ_03_BattleWounds_Complete"
 }
]